Oh, hey. We ran into your mom
at Benihana last night.
Oh. Yeah. She loves that place.
Every time they flip a shrimp in the air,
she practically leaps out of her seat to catch it.
It's why I don't take her to SeaWorld.
I know you don't want to hear it,
but she was there with Stuart.
That's fine, I don't care.
Doesn't bug you when they go on dates?
They're not dating. They're just two friends
who went out to dinner.
Then went back home
where they probably fell asleep...
...In the matching pajamas she got them
because they both just love penguins.
Hey, lots of people wear matching pajamas
who aren't dating.
-Like who?
-Like you and your dog.
Don't rule out the dating.
-Fine, it bothers me. You happy?
-You think you've got problems.
The gibbon is the only member
of the ape family not classified as a great ape.
How is this helpful?
All the non-human apes
are classified as great apes, except one.
That means taxonomists
created the entire category of lesser ape...
...just to single out the poor gibbon
as the weird kid on the playground.
Now, there's a hairy little fella
with a genuine beef.
But the gibbon doesn't know
what it's categorized as.
-It doesn't even know it's called a gibbon.
-True.
Sorry, kid. You got it worse than a gibbon.
-Hi.
-Hey.
We brought snacks for movie night.
Great. I don't suppose
you also brought napkins...
...Clean bowls,
utensils and a roll of toilet paper?
-Right here.
“Ah!
-You guys are the best.
“What's with the clothes?
With all the new stuff I bought for work,
I needed room in my closet.
I meant why are they folded. But whatever.
-Ooh. What's this?
-That, believe it or not, is my prom dress.
Wow, you still have it?
I Just assumed it was balled up
in the corner of a barn somewhere.
What kind of teenager did you think I was?
-Slutty.
-Easy.
The word is "popular.”
-How was your prom? Did you go?
-No, but I was on cleanup crew.
-Aw. That's sad.
-No, it was okay.
The DJ let me dance one slow song
with my mop before he shut down.
Whenever I see a bucket of dirty water,
I still hear "Lady in Red."
My prom was pretty terrible too.
I was excited about my date, but turned out
he only asked me because he liked my friend.
-He spent the whole night talking about her.
-We get it, you had a friend and a date.
Stop bragging.
-It doesn't matter. Prom is silly anyway.
-Easy for you to say.
-You went with the captain of the football team.
-Uh, no.
I Just made out with him a little
while his date was puking. Heh.
My date would've had to clean that up.
I have an idea.
Maybe we can have, like, a prom do-over.
That would be so much fun. We could decorate
the roof and make the guys wear tuxedoes.
Get our hair done and slow dance.
Guys, trust me, as someone
who's been to seven proms...
...It Is never as good as you want it to be.
You went to seven proms?
Yeah, let's see. Four "Under the Seas,”
two "Enchanted Evenings"...
...and one "Night to Remember"
that I cannot remember for the life of me.
-Hey.
-Hey. Where's Bernadette?
She and Amy are dress shopping
for their prom thing.
Oh, yeah. I got that Evite.
Ever since I saw Pretty in Pink,
I've wanted to go to an American prom.
But then I saw Carrie
and I did not wanna go to an American prom.
But then I saw Never Been Kissed
and I'm back on the prom bandwagon.
This prom thing
has been a real roller coaster.
Bernie's really excited.
I mean, I could tell, because her voice got
so high the beagle next door started howling.
-Did you go to your prom?
-No. Heh.
I had a date with a proper education.
Instead of a tuxedo,
I dressed myself in good habits.
Instead of spiked punch,
I enjoyed the intoxicating flavor of knowledge.
Instead of dancing in a gym,
I shook my booty to the seductive rhythms--
Okay, okay.
--of AP calculus.
How come you're not shopping?
Let me guess,
you think the whole idea is lame?
Who cares what I think. What do you think?
To be honest, it's kind of a dream come true
to go to even a fake prom...
...with a woman as beautiful as you.
Ugh. Thanks a lot.
-What?
-Now I can't blow this off without being a bitch.
That sounds like a yes.
Ooh. Every single person RSVP'd yes.
This is so exciting.
[HIGH-PITCHED]
Isn't this exciting?
[DOG HOWLING]
Yep. Heh.
Look, even Stuart's bringing a date.
I wonder who it is.
You know exactly who it is.
He's gonna bring my mom.
Why did you even invite him?
Because he's our friend
and you two need to get along.
Why can't he take your mom?
You took her to your prom.
I didn't take her. She was a chaperone.
I saw a picture of you two dancing together.
What was I gonna do?
They were playing our song.
I can't take this anymore.
[PHONE RINGS]
-Hello?
HOWARD: Stuart, we have to talk.
This thing with you and my mom,
I hate it. It's making me crazy.
You and I were friends for years.
And now you're bringing my mother
to a party I'm going to?
What the hell?
I'm not bringing your mother, I have a date.
Oh, so now you're cheating on my mother?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you talking about? There's nothing
weird going on with me and your mother.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Stewie, your bath is getting cold!
I gotta go. Bye.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
SHELDON:
Penny. Penny. Penny.
Penny. Penny.
-You knocked more than usual.
-Next time I might be in a rush...
-...It's good to have a few in the bank.
-Okay, what's up?
I'd like to discuss this party
that Amy and Bernadette are throwing.
Since you and I are reluctant to go...
...| think I've come up
with the perfect way for us to enjoy it.
-Great. How?
-We pretend we're aliens.
I'm not the best at reading facial cues...
...but I'm gonna say that you love it
and wanna hear more.
Now, in the beloved novel
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy...
...an alien named Ford Prefect
pretended to be human in order to blend in...
...So that he could write an entry about Earth
for The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
Which is a travel book
within the actual book.
Which is also called
The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
Okay, just one question. What?
My point is, pretending to be an alien
is a valuable coping mechanism...
...I've used many times.
I did it the first time
I went to see you in a play.
You had no idea Commander Un-Frump
of Seti Alpha-3 was in the audience.
Oh, don't worry.
He gave you seven thumbs up.
Okay, here's a question.
As an alien pretending to be human...
...are you planning to engage
in any post-prom mating rituals with Amy?
There are post-prom mating rituals?
Not always. Unless your date drives a van
with an air mattress. Then always.
Well, if it's part of the prom experience,
then I'm open to it.
You're kidding.
I may be an alien, but I have urges.
If Amy wants to copulate
by firing her eggs into space...
...well, then I will happily catch them with
the reproductive sac on my upper flermin.
I'm not the best at reading facial cues,
but I can see that you're a little turned on.
If you're not gonna learn how to do this,
they make some pretty good clip-ons.
Bruce Wayne doesn't wear a clip-on.
Bruce Wayne doesn't make his roommate
tie it for him.
His name is Alfred, and, yes, he does.
There, perfect.
Are you sure?
It's my first prom, I wanna do it correctly.
I thought you were gonna be an alien.
I was, but Penny didn't want to
and you didn't want to.
Bernadette, Amy, Koothrappali
and Wolowitz didn't want to.
And even I knew it was weird
to hire somebody.
-Was that a flask?
Yes.
I've decided to embrace all of the traditions
associated with prom...
...Including spiking the punch.
You're gonna put alcohol in the punch?
Oh, no, this is pomegranate juice.
It's all the fun of high school high jinks
with a cell-protecting zip of antioxidants.
If you had ripped jeans and a leather jacket...
...you'd be the toughest kid
on the Disney Channel.
So anything else planned for tonight?
Oh, everything.
Getting our picture taken, slow dancing...
...being elected prom king.
Pointing out that kings aren't elected.
It's gonna be off the hook.
And while you're at it...
...| know that at this age,
your hormones are raging...
...but just because all your friends
are having sex doesn't mean you have to.
Why would you say that?
You know, because a lot of people
lose their virginity on prom night.
Penny implied the same thing. Is this true?
Just relax, it's a joke.
You don't have hormones.
-Wow, you look amazing.
-Thank you, so do you.
Sheldon, you look so handsome.
Thank you.
Sheldon, doesn't Amy look hot?
That's gotta put some starch
in the upper flermin.
What's that?
It's a scaly genital organ
that grows between his shoulder blades.
Try not to touch it when you're dancing.
-Excuse me.
-Where are you going?
I can't do this. For your information, the flermin
doesn't rub between my shoulder blades...
...It grows out of the belly button
on my neck.
He's right.
I was thinking of the lower flermin.
Oh, I'll text Stuart, let him know we're close.
That's a neat tattoo.
Oh, thanks, it's Sally
from Nightmare Before Christmas.
That movie's so cute.
You like her
because you both have red hair?
A little, but more that she's covered in scars
and can pull her own limbs off...
_and sew them back on.
I like Cinderella.
Did you know in the original book,
the sisters cut off their toes with knives. ..
...In order to fit in the glass slipper?
I like "Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo."
-Here comes Stuart and his date.
-Oh, she's cute.
-Oh, my God.
“What?
-That's Jeanie.
-That's Jeanie?
-Who's Jeanie?
-Don't say it.
That's Howard's cousin that he had sex with.
She's my second cousin. We were 15.
I just said, don't say it.
No, it's okay,
he told me that story a long time ago.
-Raj.
- It was our first date. ..
...there was an awkward silence,
what was I supposed to say?
[GASPS]
Oh, it's beautiful.
Heh. The girls really did a nice job.
I know I wasn't into this before, but I'm so glad
I get to take you to your first prom.
What makes you think
I didn't go to my prom? I went.
-Who'd you go with?
- I took a little lady I like to call loneliness.
-Aw.
-No, it's all right.
We ended up having a threesome
with her friend humiliation.
If I'd have been there and saw you,
I would've asked you to dance.
-No, you wouldn't have.
-You don't know that.
-It was before my growth spurt. Ha-ha.
-What? That already happened?
Very funny.
-Well, you wouldn't have asked me either.
-I would have asked you. In my head.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
On the way home.
While I was having a good cry.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-Sheldon? Can I come in?
- I don't think that's a good idea.
Why not?
According to an online message board,
I may be having a panic attack.
SoccerMom09 had similar symptoms.
But to be fair,
the twins were a real handful that day.
You're making me worry. What's going on?
What's going on
IS we're about to go to a prom...
...and there's a great deal of pressure
on couples like us...
...to engage in what Mr. Bob Eubanks
called "making whoopee."
What pressure?
All I said was you look handsome.
Can you please open the door?
It's not just that.
Leonard and Penny
also made comments about it.
And I'm not blind. Even I looked twice when
I saw my posterior in these tuxedo pants.
So I met Jeanie at your Aunt Gladys's.
She passed me the Manischewitz,
I took one look at this punim...
...and almost plotzed on the kugel.
Is this what I sound like
when I talk about India?
So my mother's okay with this?
Why would she have a problem
with me and Stuart?
Because they have a weird,
inappropriate relationship.
Weirder than what you and I did
in my dad's Corolla?
-This is so messed up.
- I know, I'm having the best time.
Why would you even come to this?
Didn't you know I'd be here?
It was a long time ago, Howard.
And you're only second cousins.
Who cares?
Wait, so you knew
and you brought her anyway?
So she's good enough for Howard...
-...but not for me?
-Yeah.
Have weird relationships with your
own mother and cousin. This is his turf.
Yeah.
Well, I might not have asked you
to dance then, but I will ask you now.
-But there's no music.
-I don't care. We'll make our own music.
My God, who's the dork now?
[LEONARD CHUCKLES]
Thank you for wearing your flats.
Thank you for wearing your heels.
Look at me, dancing with
the prettiest girl at the prom.
Wanna take a picture of us and send it
to your old friends in the Chess Club?
I sent them a bikini shot of you years ago.
This IS nice.
-I kind of wish no one else was coming.
- I know. Me too.
But it will be fun to have a prom
without all the drama.
[MEN GRUNTING]
Howie, get off of him.
Not until he stops humping his way
up my family tree.
Sheldon, this is silly.
I'm not missing another prom.
I'm going upstairs now. Goodbye.
I really did think you looked pretty.
You did?
Yes.
So much so that I started to panic.
Well, you can relax.
Just because you think I look pretty doesn't
mean we have to spend the night together.
Were you hoping we would
because it's prom?
I'm always hoping.
But tonight I just wanted
to have a nice time with you.
And maybe dance with someone
who has arms.
-Thank you for understanding.
-Of course I understand.
Sheldon. ..
...there's something else I've been
wanting to say, but before I do, I just--
I want you to know
that you don't have to say it back.
I know you're not ready and I don't want you to
say it just because social convention dictates--
I love you too.
You said it.
There's no denying I have feelings for you
that can't be explained in any other way.
I briefly considered
that I had a brain parasite.
But that seems even more far-fetched.
The only conclusion was love.
[PANTING]
I know what's happening.
This is a panic attack.
SoccerMom09 says to lie down
with your feet elevated.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Just because I love you doesn't mean
girls are allowed in my room.
RAJESH:
Okay. Here we go.
Say cheese.
Say cousin.
Say--
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hang on. Heh. Sorry.
Hey, Debbie.
Uh, yeah, I'm here with Jeanie.
Okay, but we're just friends. It's--
Yeah. I gotta go.
[English - US - SDH]